Finding Aid for Solar Car Team (University of Michigan) records, 1985-2009
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- 2000 & 2001 Accessions
  Maize & Blue (1993) (.2 linear feet) includes a small amount of information about administrative and design issues. Most of the documents relating to this vehicle, however, can be found in the materials accessioned in 1994.
  Solar Vision (1995) (.8 linear feet) contains files from the various design teams as well as those compiled by a mechanical engineering class whose task it was to design a jack for the solar car. Also included is information about the team itself.
  Wolverine (1997) (.4 linear feet) also contains files pertaining to the design and testing of this vehicle and sponsor information.
  The Maize & Blue (1999) and M-Pulse (2001) subseries (.1 linear feet) contain very limited information regarding these projects, but it is expected that more thorough documentation will be accessioned at a future date.
  - Visual Materials
    - Videocassettes (Box 10)
      - GM Sunraycer Qualifiers (U-matic), Undated (Box 10)
      - University of Michigan, Sunrunner (Construction) (VHS), 1990 (Box 10)
      - Sunrayce 1990 Winner's circle, 1990 (U-matic) (Box 10)
      - George Ettenheim, Information on Australia
        - Tape #1 (VHS), August 2, 1990 (Box 10)
        - Tape #2 (VHS), August 2, 1990 (Box 10)
        - Tape #3 (VHS), August 2, 1990 (Box 10)
        - Tape #4 (VHS), August 2, 1990 (Box 10)
        - Tape #5 (VHS), August 3, 1990 (Box 10)
      - Race Route Survey?
        - Day Four, Tape One (VHS), June 24, 1992 (Box 10)
        - Day Seven, Tape One (VHS), June 27, 1992 (Box 10)
        - Day Seven, Tape Two (VHS), June 1992 (Box 10)
      - Maize & Blue, Testing and Body fabrication (U-matic), 1992 (Box 10)
      - Maize & Blue, Testing and Body inspection, MIS (U-matic), 1992 (Box 10)
      - Join the Winning Team, Maize & Blue, The University of Michigan Solar Car (VHS), 1993 (Box 10)
      - University of Michigan College of Engineering, Maize & Blue, Sunrayce 93 (VHS), 1993 (Box 10)
      - Hail to the Victors, Sunrayce (VHS), 1993 (Box 10)
      - Sunrayce 95, Highlights of Race and Official Standings (VHS), 1995 (Box 10)
      - Sunrayce 95, Racing for the Future (VHS) (Box 10)
      - Sunrayce 95
        - Day Two, Tape Two (VHS) (Box 10)
        - Day Five, Tape One (VHS) (Box 10)
        - Day Seven, Tape Two (VHS) (Box 10)
    - Photographs
      - "Sunrunner Photos/Slides--1990 Pre-Australia" (Box 10)
        (Photographs, slides, transparencies, and negatives from binder; also includes 7/15/1991 University Record with Sunrunner 'retirement' article)
      - "Sunrunner Images Vol. II--Post Warren Win, CoE Reception/Levin, Team in DC, Australia Send-Off" (Box 10)
        (Photographs and slide from binder)
      - Solar Vision album, 1995 (Volume 1)
      - Sunrayce 95 albums, 1995; 6 folders (Box 11)
  - Sunrunner (1990)
    - General
      - Business/Administration/Operations, 1991-1999 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, General, 1989-1992 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, GM Sunrayce rules, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, Memos from Susan Fancy, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
      - Dean's Cabinet Proposal (Box 11)
      - Department of Energy, 1990 (Box 11)
      - Design concept/Vehicle specs, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
      - Design Group Leader applications, [1989] (Box 11)
      - Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
      - Events, 1990 (Box 11)
      - GM Sunrayce Workshop transcripts, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Information for proposal assistance, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Presentations, 1989 (Box 11)
      - Testing logs, 1990 (Box 11)
      - Timelines, 1990 (Box 11)
      - Timelines/Task lists/Agendas, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
    - Group Files
      - Administration, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
      - Body structure, 1989-1990 (Box 11)
      - Driveline, 1989; undated (Box 11)
      - Exterior1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Interior, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
      - Power Electronics, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
      - Solar Cells, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Solar Vision (1995)
    - Sunrayce, 1990
      - Pre-race, 1990 (Box 12)
      - Race logistics, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
      - Race updates, 1990 (Box 12)
      - Post race, 1990 (Box 12)
      - Memorabilia, 1990; 2 folders (Box 12)
        (includes sheet with team's signatures)
    - World Solar Challenge, 1990
      - Australia essays, 1990 (Box 12)
      - Pre-race, 1990; 3 folders (Box 12)
      - Race updates, 1990; 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Memorabilia, 1990 (Box 12)
  - Maize & Blue (1993)
    - Administrative, 1991; 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Solar cells, 1990-1992; 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Public Relations, 1993; 3 folders (Box 12)
    - Sunrayce, 1993 (Box 12)
    - World Solar Challenge, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Maize and Blue Press Releases, 1990-1993 (Box 12)
    - Maize and Blue Pictures, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Aerodynamics/Body, 1991-1994; 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Engineering Committee minutes
      - General, 1994 (Box 12)
      - Chassis subgroup, 1994; 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Aerodynamics/Body subgroup, 1994 (Box 12)
    - Failure Mode & Effects Analysis (FMEA), 1990-1997; 4 folders (Box 13)
    - Motor Controller: Design & spec sheets, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Power Team, 1992-1995; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Solar Car Lifting Device, ME 450, Winter 1995; 7 folders (Box 13)
    - Strategy, 1991-1995; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Team information, 1994 (Box 13)
  - Wolverine (1997)
    - "Black Book" preliminary designs, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
    - Body/Accessories, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
    - Chassis, 1996-1997; 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Front suspension, 1996; undated (Box 13)
    - Rear suspension, 1997; undated (Box 13)
    - Sponsor information (Box 13)
    - Structural reports, 1994-1997 (Box 13)
    - Suspension/Brakes, 1996; undated (Box 13)
    - Team reports, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
    - Testing log, 1996-1997 (Box 13)
  - MaizeBlaze (1999)
    - General, 1999; undated (Box 13)
  - M-Pulse (2001)
    - Sponsorship Proposal Packet, 2001 (Box 13)
- 2004 Accessions
  This accession is arranged alphabetically, which is how the records were originally kept by the solar car team. The Solar Vision subseries (1 linear ft.) has information on corporate sponsorships for the Solar Vision (1995) race team. Other files interspersed throughout have information on the car, team communications, and race information. Four files with information on Maize and Blue, the 1993 entry, have been place in Box 12 with other records pertaining to that year's car. These include pictures of the team and car, press releases, and Sunrayce 1993. the Student Papers subseries consists of papers written by student project members on varying subjects dealing with engineering aspects of the solar car. The papers were written for different classes, mostly Mechanical Engineering (ME) 490 the independent study class, within the school of Engineering pertaining to the solar car team from 1989 to 1999. Some of the student papers deal with meetings, team goals, and team evaluations. Access to the student papers is restricted under FERPA regulations.
  - Solar Vision (1994-1995)
    - Ann Arbor Earth Festival, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Abbott Laboratories, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Accounting Plan, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Accu-tech Industries, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Alcoa, 1992-1994 (Box 14)
    - Alumni Association, 1993-1994 (Box 14)
    - APX International, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Auto Show, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - Autchins, Chuck, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Baker, Lisa, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Bell, Lon, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Biel, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Boeing, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Briggs International, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Business School, 1994 (Box 14)
    - CAD Diagrams, 1994 (Box 14)
    - CAEN, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Campbell's Soup Company, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Chevrolet, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Cole, David, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Cosovich, Jon, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Dana Corporation, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Dateline, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Deans
      - Banks, Peter, 1994 (Box 14)
      - Parsons, Michael, 1994 (Box 14)
      - Smith, Gene, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Delco-Remy, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Detroit Edison, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Development Meeting, 5/19/1994 (Box 14)
    - Downs Herold, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Duderstadt, James J., 1994 (Box 14)
    - Dupont, 1994 (Box 14)
    - E160, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Eagle Picher, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Edison Electric Institute, 1994 (Box 14)
    - EDS, 1994 (Box 14)
    - E-mail, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Equity Financial Management, 1994 (Box 14)
    - ERIM, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Faculty/Financial Advisor, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Fairlane Gear, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Ford Motor Company, 1994 (Box 14)
    - General Automotive, 1994 (Box 14)
    - General Motors, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Gerhart, Ro, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Guardian Industries, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Harrison, Walt, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Howard Delivery Services, 1994 (Box 14)
    - ITT Auto, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Kilsby Roberts, 1994 (Box 14)
    - King, Richard, 1994 (Box 14)
    - LSA, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Masco Corporation, 1994 (Box 14)
    - MCI Communications Corporation, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Michigan International Speedway, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Marion Merrell Dow, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Monroe Auto Equipment, 1994 (Box 14)
    - M-TEC, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Motorola, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Nelson, Nancy, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Nova Metal, 1994 (Box 14)
    - NTN Tech, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Photos, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Project Manager Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 14)
    - Public Relations Plan, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Public Relations, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Whitaker, Gil, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - Race Route Information, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
    - Race Rules, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Reebok, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Recruitment, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Rockwell, 1994 (Box 14)
    - SAC, 1994 (Box 14)
    - SAP, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Silicon Graphics, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Solar Express, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Sponsor Thank You Letters, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Sprint Corporation, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Sunrayce 1995 Proposal Original 1993 (Box 14)
    - Sunrayce 1995 Race Information 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Team Elections, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Trick Titanium, 1994 (Box 14)
    - TQM, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Unistrut, 1994 (Box 14)
    - University Officials, 1994 (Box 14)
    - UPS, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Vehma International, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Vice President
      - Hartford, Maureen, 1994 (Box 14)
      - Kennedy, Richard, 1994 (Box 14)
      - Neal, Homer, 1994 (Box 14)
      - Williams, Frank, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Wawro, Matt, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Willowtree Apartments, 1994 (Box 14)
    - World Solar Challenge, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Yaskawa, 1994 (Box 14)
  - Student Papers
    - Sunrunner (1990)
      - Transmission Design for the University of Michigan Solar Car, 1989 (Box 15)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1 2074 ]
      - Solar Car Project, 1989 (Box 15)
      - Sunrunner: The Engineering Report, 1990 (Box 15)
      - Sunrunner: An Overview, 1990 (Box 15)
      - Sunrunner Account Information, 1991 (Box 15)
    - Maize and Blue (1993)
      - Final Report, 1991 (Box 15)
      - Design of the Solar Car Braking System, 1992 (Box 15)
      - University of Michigan Maize and Blue Project Update Report for Electronics Team, 1992 (Box 15)
      - A Basic Approach to Battery Optimization, 1992 (Box 15)
      - Final Report, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Project Management, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Maize and Blue, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Optimization of Available Energy in Solar Vehicle Competition, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Exterior Fabrication, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Power System, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Driver's Report for the Maize and Blue Solar Car Project, 1993 (Box 15)
      - Maize and Blue and Solar Vision Projects, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Engineering Report, The, 1994 (Box 15)
      - My Solar Car Experience, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Solar Vision (1995)
      - Solar Car Body Construction, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Report, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Look Inside the Construction, Materials, and Properties of a U of M Solar Car, 1995 (Box 15)
      - Design, Analysis, and Manufacture of the Wheels for Solar Vision, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Designing a "Solar Vision", 1994 (Box 15)
      - Front Suspension Design, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Brake System, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Introduction to the Selection Processes and Modeling Techniques of Lead-acid Batteries in Solar/Electric Vehicle Applications, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Design Trade-off Analysis with Custom Software, 1994 (Box 15)
      - Engineering Committee Report, 1994; 2 folders (Box 15)
      - Power Systems Report, 1994 (Box 15)
      - University of Michigan Solar Car, 1995 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Project: The Educational Experience, 1995 (Box 15)
      - Design and Construction of "Solar Vision's" Solar Array, 1995 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Jack, 1995 (Box 15)
      - The Solar Vision Project: My Involvement, What I Learned, and What I would Change, 1996 (Box 15)
      - On-Board Computer, 1996 (Box 15)
      - Aerodynamic Design of a Solar/Electric Vehicle for Entry into the 1996 World Solar Challenge 1995 (Box 15)
      - Going the Distance: The Solar Car Experience, 1996 (Box 15)
      - Senior Design Project, 1996 (Box 15)
      - Multiple Replications Method and Joint Distributions Method for UM Solar Car Teams SVSim Software, 1996 (Box 15)
      - Preparation for the Race Route Survey, 1996 (Box 15)
      - The Wolverine Experience, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Testing the Motor for "The Car", 1997 (Box 15)
      - Management of the UM Solar Car Team, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Charging Structure Final Report, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Integrating the UM Solar Car Team with Academics, 1997 (Box 15)
      - True Lessons from the Development of the Rear Suspension, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Driving Wolverine: Comparison of Closed Testing, Circle Track Racing, Road Testing, and Road Racing, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Effects of Student Project Teams on the Educational Experience of UM Students, 1998 (Box 15)
      - Solar Car Projects, 1998 (Box 15)
    - MaizeBlaze (1999)
      - MaizeBlaze: See You in the Winner's Circle, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Advanced Composites Research and Design, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Update Report: Composite Curing Oven, 1998 (Box 15)
      - Design and Fabrication of 4a "Flexible" Oven Controller for Use by the UM Solar Car Team, 1998 (Box 15)
      - Project Report: Steering Design for Sunrayce 99, 1998 (Box 15)
      - The Project Team Experience, 1998 (Box 15)
      - Designing a Lighter Wheel, 1998 (Box 15)
      - Turning Dreams into Reality: The Administrative Operations of a Solar Car Team, 1999 (Box 15)
      - Sunrayce 99 Entry Proposal, 1999 (Box 15)
- 2007 Accession
  The 2007 Accession consists entirely of visual materials, 11 videocassettes in total. The videocassettes have been arranged by solar car. Most of the videocassettes are from the original solar car, Sunrunner. The others are on the second car, Maize & Blue. The topics of the videocassettes range from different races the cars competed in to issue updates on the car to media reports on the cars.
  - Visual Material
    - Videocassettes (Box 16)
      - Sunrunner: The Australia Challenge (VHS) (Box 16)
      - Sunrunner: Running with the Sun, Down Under, USA & Australia (VHS) (Box 16)
      - 1990 World Solar Challenge 1990 (VHS) (Box 16)
      - Issue Update #30 GM Sunrayce USA (VHS) (Box 16)
      - 1990 World Solar Challenge: Darwin to Adelaide 1990 (VHS) (Box 16)
      - Sunrunner: USA & Australia (Slides/Music) (VHS) (Box 16)
      - Mid-Term Status Report On the Michigan Solar Car Project...the Unveiling (VHS) (Box 16)
      - Selected Scenes from GM Sunrayce USA (VHS), 1990 (Box 16)
      - Preview Media -- Sunrunner "E Report" & "Impact" (VHS), 1992 (Box 16)
      - Racing with the Sun Downunder (1993 World Solar Challenge) (VHS) (Box 16)
      - EDS Information Technology Update #2 "Sunrayce '93" (VHS), 1993 (Box 16)
- Accession, 2008
  The 2008 accession (6.5 linear feet) is comprised of files dating from1989 to 2008 the majority of which relate to the sponsorship of the University of Michigan solar cars and teams. The accession also includes files on the individual solar cars and on topics relating to their development. It is arranged into seven subseries: Website, Solar Cars, Tests, Topical Files, Visual Materials, Sponsor Files, and Student Papers.
  The Solar Car subseries (.5 linear feet) covers the years 1990 to 2007 and is arranged alphabetically by solar car. All solar cars through Continuum (2007) are represented with the majority of materials on cars that fall between Wolverine (1997) and Momentum (2005). Records include race programs, recruitment flyers, meet the team booklets, some team meeting minutes, schedules, and race information.
  The Test subseries (.25 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically and covers the years 1995 to 2001. It is made up of files relating to different test for the solar cars a significant amount of this data is wind tunnel test data.
  The Topical Files subseries 1990 to 2006 (1 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically. It contains files on various topics surrounding the solar car and the solar car team, including, presentations, inspections and analyses, meeting notes, and recognition certificates.
  The Visual Materials subseries 1990-2008 (1.25 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically and by format. The subseries has a small amount of photographs and publications. The sub-subseries Videocassettes 1990-2001 (1.0 linear feet) includes VHS tapes with footage ranging from professional produced race coverage and promotional videos to footage shot by the solar team of the team and their car.
  The Sponsor Files subseries 1989-2005 (3 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by company name. It contains the sub-subseries General 1993-2001; which includes miscellaneous sponsor files and files the team had filed by automotive part. Contents include sponsorship outreach letters, information on possible sponsors, rejection letters from sponsors, as well as, information on official solar car team sponsors.
  The Student Papers subseries 1990-2003 (.5 linear feet) is comprised of reports and papers generated by students on the solar car team. Reports cover general team reports, design and implementation, and weather forecasting. Reports were generally required in order for the students to receive course credit for their work on the solar car.
  - Solar Cars
    - Sunrunner, 1990 (Box 17)
    - Maize & Blue, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Solar Vision, 1995 (Box 17)
    - Wolverine, 1997 (Box 17)
    - MaizeBlaze, 1999; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - M-Pulse, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Spectrum, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Momentum, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Continuum, 2007 (Box 17)
  - Tests
    - MaizeBlaze Wind Tunnel Test, 1999 (Box 17)
    - M-Pulse Wind Tunnel Test, 2001 (Box 17)
    - M-Pulse-2000-2001 (Box 17)
    - Wind Tunnel Tests, 1995-1996 (Box 17)
  - Topical Files
    - 2001 World Solar Challenge Entry Form, 2001 (Box 17)
    - American Solar Challenge Notebook, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Brake Specifications and Analysis, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Budget Materials, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Buy a Cell Fundraiser, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Fall Mass Meeting Presentation, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Fire Inspection and Report, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Impact, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Meeting Notes, 2004 (Box 18)
    - O.S.E.H, 1998 (Box 18)
    - Outsourcing Buyer's Guide, 2002 (Box 18)
    - Presentation for Recruitment, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
    - Random Drawings, 2005 (Box 18)
    - Recognition Certificates, 2002-2006 (Box 18)
    - Recognition by Governor Jennifer Granholm, 2005-2006 (Box 18)
    - Research Articles and Knowledge, undated (Box 18)
    - Sketches and Notes, undated (Box 18)
    - Sunrayce Route '97, 1997 (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Solar Car Project -- Darwin to Adelaide, Australia November 11 to Project Radio System., November 17, 1990 (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Solar Car Team Business Team -- Detroit Edison Presentation, 1998 (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Solar Car Team Presentation for Bauer Controls, 2000 (Box 18)
    - University of Michigan Solar Car Team Presentation for the University of Michigan Statistics Department, 2000 (Box 18)
    - Wind Tunnel Agreement, 1999 (Box 18)
    - Wolverine Chassis Team, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Wolverine Team Presentation, 1997 (Box 18)
  - Visual Materials
    - The University of Michigan Solar Car Team -- National Champs,., 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18)
    - Produced Publications, undated (Box 18)
    - Publications Featuring the Solar Car Team, 2000-2008; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Solar Express Newsletter, 1991-1994; 1998; 2000; 2007 (Box 18)
    - Videocassetes
      - GM Sunrayce USA VNR Days 6,7,8 & 9 Wrap & B-Roll Winner's B-Roll (VHS), 1990 (Box 19)
      - Promotion Video -- Music, Not Dialog (VHS), 1993 (Box 19)
      - Promotional Video (VHS), 1993 (Box 19)
      - Australia Advising (VHS) (Box 19)
      - DTE Energy Commercial featuring 3 seconds of Wolverine (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Driving Australia (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Driving Under the Sun Governor's Cup Solar Challenge Pre-Sunrayce '90 (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Dynamic Scrutineering (VHS) (Box 19)
      - GM Promo (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Insurance Video of Washtenaw Workspace (VHS), 4/18/1996 (Box 19)
      - Loading Solar Vision into Trailer Upper Surface Handling Techniques (Box 19)
      - MaizeBlaze at Greenfield Village (Unveiling) Channel 4 Action News with Chuck Gaidica (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Maize & Blue -- Detroit Auto Show, 7 January 1993 Public Unveiling, Power Ctr., 20 March 1993 (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Maize and Blue February '93 Testing and Development (VHS) (Box 19)
      - M-Pulse Unveiling (VHS), 4/11/2001 (Box 19)
      - Mold Work at Christie Industries Sanding and Bonding (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Solar Vision # 1 @ Briggs (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Sunrayce '95 (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Sunrayce '95 Team Video Competition Winners (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Sunrayce '97 Wolverine University of Michigan Promotional Video (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Sunrayce '99 Kickoff Engineering Techniques (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Sunrayce '99 Kickoff Safety, Scrutineering, Logistics (VHS) (Box 19)
      - University of Michigan College of Engineering Cuts of Solar Car Races, Michigan Engineering Television Network (VHS) (Box 19)
      - University of Michigan Solar Car Team Community Television Network/ Ann Arbor (VHS), May 2001 (Box 19)
      - Wind Tunnel (old car) (Box 19)
      - Wind Tunnel Testing MaizeBlaze-Full Scale (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Wolverine and Other Teams in a New York City Parade (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Wolverine Construction (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Wolverine Construction-Lab Array (VHS) (Box 19)
      - Wolverine Construction -- Solar Cell Attachment (VHS) (Box 19)
  - Sponsor Files
    - General
      - Miscellaneous Sponsor Files, 1993; 2000-2001 (Box 20)
        [Restricted]
      - Airline, 2001 (Box 20)
      - Battery Manufacturers (Box 20)
      - Carbon Fibers (Box 20)
      - Electronics (Box 20)
      - Solar Car Team Presentation-Guide to Sponsorship, undated (Box 20)
      - Tabbing (Box 20)
      - Truck Driver Sponsorship (Box 20)
    - 3-D Systems (Box 20)
    - 3M (Automotive), 1998 (Box 20)
    - A & L Parts, Inc., 2000 (Box 20)
    - A.C. (Box 20)
    - Action Rental, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Adtech Plastics, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Advanced Composites Group, Inc., 1999 (Box 20)
    - Advanced Polymer Industries, Inc., 1999 (Box 20)
    - Advanced Radio Systems (Box 20)
    - Aeroquip, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
    - AIAG (Box 20)
    - Aironet Wireless Communications, Inc., 1998 (Box 20)
    - Airport Metals (Box 20)
    - Alarium Chemical Company, 1994 (Box 20)